Contact

7138196493 (Home) nursedavis1@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/latasha-davis-msn-rn-bc-08b0b444 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Hospitals Leadership

LaTasha Davis, MSN RN-BC

Nurse Manager/Co-owner Ladybug Drilling, LLC, Co-Owner Davellis Drilling, LLC

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

15 years of clinical nursing experience. 5 years of medical-surgical, 3 years specialty training in trauma surgical intensive care unit, and 7 years of experience in ambulatory care. Board certified ambulatory care nurse (RN-BC). Graduated with a Master of Science in Nursing with a specialization in Executive Nurse Leadership Summer 2016. Aside from my nursing career, I am co-owner of a minority owned (Women's Business Enterprise) horizontal directional drilling company, Davellis Drilling, LLC.

Experience

Harris Health System
14 years

Nurse Manager December 2014 - Present (5 years 6 months) Houston, Texas Area

Nurse Manager Family Practice Free standing clinic

Nurse Manager December 2013 - December 2014 (1 year 1 month) Houston, Texas Area

Nurse Manager Radiation Oncology Clinic

Assitant Nurse Manager
June 2009 - December 2013 (4 years 7 months)

Oversees 32 FTE's and 5 specialty clinics including Oral surgery, ENT, Plastic/Minor surgery, Ophthalmology, & Speech Pathology/Audiology Clinics. Responsible for timely patient flow, ordering supplies, employee scheduling, Kronos timekeeping, departmental budgeting, variance reports, assisting physicians in procedures, Magnet research, Evidence based practice projects, and providing leadership to all staff.

Nurse Clinician June 2006 - June 2009 (3 years 1 month) Page 1 of 2 Houston, Texas

Staff RN

Davellis Drilling, LLC
Co Owner
August 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)
Katy, TX

Davellis Drilling, LLC is a horizontal directional drilling company established in 2016 amongst friends who shared a vision of entrepreneurship. We specialize in the installation of fiber optic cable, electric, pvc, gas, and conduit. Contact info@DavellisDrilling.com for all of your boring needs.

Education

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Master of Science (M.S.), Nursing · (2014 - 2016)

University of Houston-Victoria

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2010 - 2011)

Lone Star College

Associates of Applied Science, Registered Nursing · (2004 - 2006)

Lafayette General Medical Center School of Health Sciences
Practical Nursing, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse Training (2000 - 2001)